Hey besties, welcome back to our YouTube
channel.  If you new here, my name is
Paula Kajala.  Praise be to the Lord Jesus.
Muslims are the ones who are making things difficult.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you.  And now I have chosen the Islamic name,
Ramadan Kareem.
So today we have been invited to Lamata to
break our fast, as you know this is the period
of fasting and Ramadan.  Yes.
So we've been invited to
this vlog, we'll be showing you guys,
we go to break the fast, we feed people
at Muslim places, when we're invited at
Christian places, we all invade them, we turn them on, we go to
break the fast ourselves, that's what I
was seeing, guys, many people
are asking, what religion are you guys, we're
Christians, guys,
but I'm going to be Muslim soon,
okay,
but we're still Christians until we
change our religion, and as for clothing,
we like to wear this way, as you
can see, it suits us.
So let's go to Lamata.
Wow.  What do you have to say?
No, I'm just saying, you know,
we always fast,
but during the Islamic fast, we
fry them, we really appreciate it
because when you fry them, they taste
delicious.  If Muslims
cook, they cook a lot of food,
so we can just have breakfast here,
we've made tea and the game is over.
They have tables here and there.  Oh, we wish
these fasts would continue like this, that they would be
consistent every day.
So guys, let's go to Lamata.  Bye.
Come on, come on
.
He doesn't want
this woman to have sex with
you, man. I'm the one who
gave birth to you, man.
So then.  I don't want crying
in the hallway.  Hey guys, let's go
to the king, let's go to the king, let's go
to the king, then or
where are we going,
Maringo?
Welcome guys are you in
soon where are you staying people come in
family how are
things going what is he doing he
covers himself
eating bad food and mchamba
youtube sakina
YouTube
I have arrived guys I ran before
even time the
house is beautiful
good
everyone if you
invite me for iftar know that I must
come with my handbag wallet
must be there my handbag number
two number one that's here
handbag number three is there to pick up the
food soon soon Welcome soon soon
meat help
me guys take you there guys
wherever there is food immediately almost
all the rice I am asked take all the rice
a I have been told there are many b I am
teasing you know
that is what you want me to taste today my my
bff and I have prepared
our kiteti I told him to make you iftar he told me
okay we have to
invite others because it is the
first time and he hasn't fasted what should
I tell them
we he doesn't want to know how it happened
you planned I don't know you sat in a policy meeting I don't know
you agreed that things don't concern us
we want to eat so
guys I ask him to start downloading
kajal others you will follow
because it is his aa by the way
tomorrow is my birthday so  Guys, you
will start taking care of me today until tomorrow
and my bff will be the one who starts it because he
asked for it.
Tam, you
fought, noodles,
eh noodles, cook noodles.
What are you called inside?
Tell them.
It is called a noodle soup.  People should stop telling us that we don't know how to
get there.
lips, go and
get me
seven, they
all ran away, you're cooking here, the
first bottle, if
he changed the bottle, they changed the side,
but
at
that time, until someone gets confused,
that is, it does
n't have sugar,
cooks, you
like sugar,
this means it doesn't have sugar,
there's no sugar, I don't
like it, how do
you cut it first,
just eat it, because I don't understand,
I'll go back, this is a very
good food,
10, I really liked this ground meat
with rice, rice, you have coconut, that is, if you eat it like this, you smell
coconut,
you smell coconut,
and there, imagine I haven't taken all the food,
but the food is very tasty, van
kitchen, how is the food,
10 out of 10, you take notes, there,
perfect,
my best, say, the food is very tasty,
say, oh, the
habit, that is, when someone is fasting,
you see that you are eating, that is, if you just start eating a
little, the food becomes tasty, you find yourself
full quickly, then you want to eat,
but your stomach is full, now they don't put Amira in,
you put Amira in,
no, it's just tasty, you are a ghost,
now what do you and Amila have to do with each other
here, but this one,
we,
the best, yeah, the best, and chicken  I want you to eat it, you were told it
was placed on 12 coconuts.
Have you ever seen it placed on 12 coconuts? You are the first one
like your mother. Oh, shout
to the
yeah, my people. There are people. The
food is very good.
At
first, I knew that
a few would be good, but everything he tastes
is good. Don't say this juice. I
want to completely pass out.
This juice is still the second glass.
Dangerous. The
food is very good.
Let me sayang.
Exactly
how is the food, bro? Oh, fine, fine. I give it to you in
Swahili. I give it to you.
From one to 10. How much food do you give?
Oh, this food,
sir. I give it to you.
Yo, how is the food, bro?  Delicious.
Delicious.  Yes.  10
10 over 10.
How is the food, bro?  10 over 10
Yeah.  Perfect.
Tommy out of everything you ate today,
which one's your favorite?
My favorite my favorite is mzuzu
sambusa.
Samosa.  Beans
choose one.  Just choose one.
Choose
samosa.
Samosa.  Sambrusa.
Sambrusa.
Guys thank you very much for coming guys
befong kaja kaja and his child guys invited him and brought him I
invited you faula so we
enjoyed they enjoyed
what you did I
cooked myself then I told you would you come
measure let's cook and show you how he cooks you made him come what do you do so
next I'm baking m we were
at the mansion mansion of bff guys
as you can see as
you can see we were best friends next you are coming
to Paula's mansion
next
your mansion how is
mine first it's next year
no why
but we enjoyed guys the food was
comingfurah
thank you bye bye bye bye
guys like lamata said I was
n't invited I felt like I was going crazy you
can't be you have put it in my heart
yes lamata I didn't come I didn't like
but anyways the food was good I
liked who I liked was minced meat you know I didn't like I
just found rice and
minced meat really
eh
m I liked there are those like
scones like m beehive that I
really like then and chicken
m
chicken they bake that is anaturi
even that who is liu bread to pour
but I don't know you mixed it up  and the tanki
watambi is
very good
so guys today is the seventh day for Muslims
but for Christians today is the
sixth day.
You know, because we Christians do
n't fast on Sundays.
That is, we don't close every Sunday.  We fast for
three days, we don't fast on Sundays.  So we are up
to date.
But I want to show you a recap of how
we started Ramadan and with Rezma.
We went to the market I mean Buchan we went to
buy things we went to church for
Ash Wednesday we went to Serena for
iftar I invited
Mr and Mrses Rajab at home for iftar
various events so here is a recap at what time
how many kilos and
kilos i.e. say seven kilos and kilos
but they will separate separate
they will separate
But 10 kilos you put in what i.e.
one kilo like in the mikupo
separate if
you put them like this they all freeze
eh
it becomes difficult to give
guys we came to Buchan to
buy meat kupu fish
for Ramadan and for resma
and chicken also liver kidney gift
yeah you know guys
first we have a habit of doing that but right now
Ramadan and for resma are
parallel so we have to just do the shopping
put things inside
we cook for iftar I
don't want those who are sitting too much art
I want fresh chicken I
still have liver I want there is liver
mixed with kidney and
heart I don't want liver
S or what?
Oh and that's it, I want
72, it
's 72, you don't have another one, and that's it,
you have even a GSM phone, and I want
one,
tell me the price, what price are you selling for
and I want
three,
I'm out 3,000,
3000,
oh, the bag
for 15,
please, then how many,
two, 3,000? What is that, which one is 17500
?
Both are 3500.
Oh, just give me 15 two at
your house, I
want that one, I want two,
you have ugali.  Oh, the
flour.  Hey
brother, let me pray for you
Ash Wednesday,
my boyfriend and I have come to church. Are you fasting? Are you fasting? Are
you fasting?
Okay, good girl, fit check.
I mean, imagine, we knew that mass
starts at 9 a.m., but I don't know that it starts at
11 a.m., have we just been here?
What time is it now?   It
will start there at 10:00. I don't know.
At
30:00, there won't
even be anyone.
We will stay today until we are mixed up.
What time was it yesterday?   The
time now I feel is
not 9 o'clock: I say it is not 9a.
Oh, so we've got it figured out, guys. I'm getting
confused after thinking about it for hours.
What is this?
What do you want?
That which burns.  and this one wants that has
m
ashwense
thank God we were able to arrive
and we have arrived the days have
officially started then
tomorrow I will show you now this
account
chauro chauro chauro
alfu so that we can come and talk to dad
but I spend a lot of time when I am eating,
why is it so
exciting when he
tells me to take the Jag they are there where is
that jug?  Jagiwekwa,
look at the
things to buy jugs right now, people,
we have come to finish shopping for
Ramadan and Kwarezma, this sister wants a
jug for her son,
where am I,
Vanessa Mkinga, wherever you see this video,
I ask you to buy me an air fryer please,
Vanessa Mkinga,
if it doesn't help me,
people of the vlog, this sister has given me acid medicine, if it doesn't help me, it
's really good, let me try it, I will come and
give you a review,
M lakh,
yeah, maybe it will be 5k,000, I'm not so
sure.  Let's go find out.
What's your reaction?   I'm
surprised because I've never seen a
yellow watermelon.  It's sweet,
bro.  This is sweet,
oh, it's sweet,
sweet like a watermelon.
Oh, it's a ticket,
but a yellow one.   Yellow
.   Let
its taste come.
Don't cry
now why and yellow
as guys I'm the host for today for the
fasting and my guests have arrived
beautiful lady
welcome to the mansion
thank you
welcome to the mansion thank
you are
you ready to eat iftar iftar
which has never happened
why has it not happened this is a fari where did it
come from in heaven
Oman
chapati
ngeke dod
then
thank you
I saw who
Omari made the songs
on YouTube so bad I even remembered.
Wow.
Thank you so much for the food guys.  We had
a nice baby.  Enjoy?
Yeah.  That's good.  Omar's family.
Mwanga's family.  Thank you very much.
Very close.  Welcome to our city.
Next to us we will welcome you.  You don't want
light, isn't it ahah
alf light light in English what's
better even light family family
light I hire you are light light or
what does
n't know
you know light
manga just fresh
light why fresh light light is not
light what is it
eh it
's light yourself
yourself when you get married
you change your name kaula na go
Mwanga
Omari Mwanga
Paula Mwanga
Who is that Paula's chair?  Amara Amara
Omari Wasa
is what is written
Amara Omari Mwanga
nice names
every
half there is a very hot one that does not burn
How
mi ya Serena always I like the best
that is when I
lie down I enjoy the banana mzuzo
there is that baby you taste that like pilau
pilau I don't know if you
tasted it
Yeah.  Very nice.  Serena is always amazing.
Yeah.  The best.
Always our best place to have.
Amazing.  You say all the you ate today.
Gazitam, Tambi Marage,
I like Swahili things.
So I really enjoyed it.  Thank you so much,
baby.  I want to thank my mother.
How are you doing,
mom and dad, thank you for the stari. God
bless you. Get down to business.
Bye
guys, meet my family.
This is my baby.  This is my little baby.
Amara says hi.
Say hi.
Say I'm the little superstar.   He's
breaking those glasses right now, I'm
telling you.
We went to knit with my boyfriend.
Why did my boyfriend stretch?  And she's
never had her hair done at a salon and is being
followed home every day?  I regretted it.
Amara Amara Amara Amara Amara Amara Amara Amara Amara
Amara
Okay.  Say hi guys.
Say hi.   Don't
turn it off.  Why do you want to turn off the lights?
She's a hater.
Then he didn't want us to sit down.  He
wanted us to dance while we were standing and yet, oh
my, he kept bothering us and crying.  Oh,
Amari, he knew how to straighten me out.  We had to
go to Fahal's place so that the princess
would stop bothering us.
Amara is a food.  In other words, when the chips came,
he completely forgot that he was being teased and
calmed down.
Tell me your mother without saying it.
Hi
bye
bye bye bye
bye.   You say goodbye to
your bad behavior.  Why do you
mean
tell him kiss kiss kiss
om bye
kiss kiss kiss kiss.
Hey
five
baby fingers.
Okay, then, then,
okay, show me your mouth.  Show me your
mouth.  Show me your ears.  Ears
head.
Noss.
Good girl eyes.
Head,
nose, mouth, ears.  Yay.  Shoulders
shoulder.
Come on, gang.
Here we were finished.  I was
trying to snap him but he was
surprised by the light.  But thank you,
Jandro.
I hope you enjoyed our recap.  See you
tomorrow.
I've seen so many people
wanting me to play a prank.  So I start
pranking Mrs. Amara.  I tell him I came
home and found Amara with a sign.
His sister hit him, I mean I saw her on
camera hitting him or squeezing him or whatever, a
lie, that is, it will happen right there while I'm
hitting him.  So let's go and call him.
I've put on Mara lipstick here.
His grandmother doesn't really believe he's done
anything.  Now I don't know whether to say he's been squeezed, I don't know
.  Let me call his wife,
guys.  She's calling.
What has Amani suffered?
Oh, not this one, but he left it
on the stairs himself.
But what am I not forbidding you guys?
If you tell me, someone will answer me, I
will kill this Maka.
What does he answer you?
He tells me now that the person himself is struggling, what should I do
?
Really, guys, if they say that a child is
struggling,
I myself am surprised.
You are the one who says that a child is struggling.
When a child is struggling, you are the one who says that a child is struggling. When a child is struggling, you know, you have to
look at him. You are the one who says that he is struggling. That is, he is really struggling. That is, he is struggling. Now, he is struggling. There is no
doubt about that. There is no doubt that a child is
struggling. What is he doing on the stairs? He
must leave
every day. I say, don't leave a child
on the stairs.
No, not in sight. I send a
voice note. Guys, send a voice note. Wait,
what is his job if a child is
struggling? What does it mean if someone is struggling with
his job, watching a child, then the
child has defeated him. Just wait. I will tell him
that it's a prank. He is very panicked. Let me call him.
It's a prank. He
will answer like this. It's a prank.
Tell him it's a prank. Baby, how many times have
they put lipstick on me?
Talk like this.
Do you know how many people have you shocked? How
many sisters?
You know how many people you've let down but
how many sisters were shaking here
and I'll tell them, answer me, tell me now he was
bothering me, what should I do now,
what's wrong with you, you, don't do this again,
hey besties, so today is a photoshoot,
as you all know, he is a brand ambassador
for Real Moment Studios, I will put them on
their Instagram so you can take them and
your children to take pictures, so he went to take
pictures of Ramadan,
but I was afraid to go with him
because if
he sees you shaking, he will be very worried and I
knew he would cry, we don't want to take
pictures.  So Uncle Shan went ahead with
his sister, then later I said let me
just go, but by the time I arrived, he
had already finished shooting.
After that, we went to Dalia's
to buy her some clothes because most of her clothes
were starting to fall off, along
with her shoes.  So let me show you how
the whole day went.
take this one
and I'm embarrassed,
man, soon in our kids outfit store,
my customer, this Paula, imagine
before she even gave birth, when she just got
her friend, she opened the gift, it's for
Dalia, who was born, now we're shopping
all the way from the nursery to now, all the clothes,
hey my loves, it's another beautiful day,
today I want to go visit
my friend, she has given birth, so I want to go
see the baby and send her a gift, but
man, forehead, mamchakanga,
amara, her father, and her mother-in-law, but I
came to discover today that I have a mother-in-law, but
anyways,
my dress is fromel stylist,
she ate on this dress,
but the mother wants to be blamed, man.
This is today's post, I don't even know how
I got it, but anyway, I've already gone out
to see the baby, congratulations my
friends, but my friend did
n't want to be criticized in the first place
because she hasn't posted yet that she gave birth
or that she was pregnant.
But anyways I'm happy I met the child
I wish the family would go back to being small like that right now it
's a mess
I arrived in Serena at this time my father has
come to Dar es Salaam he's working in Arusha
so I haven't seen him for almost four months he just
arrived I want to go
see him.  I'm so excited.
Let's go see the handsome old man.
What's up Mr.   a
little lower like this just took the wind
I just told her
we are called hearts right by the river right now you
won't understand until it's over
hi bes
hi
so this lady here ran away from me almost
three days she traveled we will show in
the next vlogger where did she go and
what did she go to do?  I haven't seen him for three days,
and I mean, not seeing him for three days is
not normal, I feel sick.  So I
told him, let's catch up and go on a date.
But hey, Frida is in love
but she's not, that is, she does
n't know about Amara, Fida doesn't know about Paula, that's how it
works.  Two days
ago my son was very upset and had a fever
so I told him because he was sick
he said sorry and hung up the phone listen let me
tell you that I didn't hang up the
phone yesterday I don't like how often he breaks the same
thing because
he cries a lot this is not the
first time because he gets fever he is bothered every day we put the same thing on him so
I don't like not hugging him he cries like that I feel sorry for him
every day when he hugs you don't you know
eh I feel sorry for him I see that he is suffering he is hurting that's
why
I hung up my phone my mistake I didn't do it again
but you know I care about them a
lot and I love them
imagine I told them here let's go on a date she
came with her husband i.e. here he has
only left for a minute
now he has said he can't live without me
sir no because I was with him I am in the
city there are things we were doing
there he is escorting the bank
Now I had to tell him to just let us go eat and
go home.
But anyway, no problem, I know
my place.  I know
the place exists.  But anyway, we came
here to eat.  The place is very beautiful.
You mean a lot to me.  The view is nice.
I love you.
I love you more.
You are my soul.  You are
my favorite.  My life without you is
impossible.  And it's impossible.   I
've figured it out, I know
even Rajabu himself knows, he tells me
that you are everything and then he is the one who
follows, so
guys,
the place here is very nice, the view
around,
play like an Indian, now
play that, I'm serious, you know, how do I play?
We play with that outfit, you'll look good.  One,
two, three.  Let's go.
Hey, a little further down,
Kajala,
my aunt has arrived here, we were
waiting for her to eat iftar together.
Mom, can you see my aunt?
I see him.  Why are you blaming me?
I myself don't understand.
Why don't you have anything, sir?
That is, until we find you and caress you.
Who are you?  Princesses of the garden.
You're in love, you're in love, I don't understand why
I'm even looking for you, it's so
strange.
Are you married?
I'm not a pana.  Because I don't understand, I just see
things on the internet.  I'm
not s hey
hi
he we miss you.
You've slowed down, man. Yes, by the way,
by the way, I'm aming.  I'm fasting.  I'm
fasting.  Praying for us
of course.  Pray for who is praying for you?  Who
else?  No one.
I pray a lot for my brothers but I miss them so much
.  You fast, yes, I do
n't
fast, I'm the only one who fasts,
but mom doesn't fast, you see her
there, she's drunk, you
don't fast, why do you fast me,
Paula, you fast, I fast,
I said these last ones, my friends, you
're sleeping, I'm skinny, how are you doing? We're
just going down and we see her. Oh,
please come and check the things you said,
you've taken my legs away.  Haha.
Don't sell me because if you just sell me you know these
pictures are deleted,
man, there are pictures of a van for duumbuka
in that section, there are games,
I don't know, and the boss sold them to me, I deleted those
pictures and I haven't given them to him until today, they are
good,
he sold them to me, tell him not to sell them to me and here
I should give him his pictures
and say, "Oh my
god, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, man, what is it or people, even you, no, my friend, show me what he would do, sir. I
saw it in Paula, but you talked
like you were throwing away
his soul, you don't know his stuff, he's the
best,
so today to vision and I was my best for
my
meat, you're killing me, you're
not shang.
No.   I'm going to
Navaza, he takes the bag, he closes it, he enters the room, he gets here,
bravo,
we meet, get dressed,
okay, Ramadhani Karim, why don't you say something,
children, in
fact, among the things you shouldn't
forget is to subscribe,
subscribe
or subscribe,
oh,
what's up,
our Kajala and Paula channel, and
continue to see our
daily things because every day we are in
this family.  Now, don't confuse the
name he mentioned.  The name means
YouTube.  This one.  Subscribe.  Subs.  Um
the food was really nice and I just want
to thank my husband for watching my
eating.  So
I wish Ramadan would continue.
Understand?  Because I'm eating healthy
and the food was nice.  Or what do you say?
Yeah.
The food was nice.
But my wife has just become an
economist.  when it comes to the economy,
the lesson on economics will continue because it takes
what we need, we don't have, we don't want to
spend money for some time, we
get rich, so if you want to be rich, you got to
keep money, you understand, so any
money comes around, we don't spray out
when we see money, and we don't throw out money,
you understand, like, understand,
so we keep it up, so I'm a
little stressed out,
you say, soon, we'll see you again,
the food was so amazing, very nice, perfect,
amazing, I love seafood,
I went to
my place on the prone plate, fish fillet,
bye, bye, hi,
guys, hi,
today, my baby, he's sick, he's caught a cold, he's caught a cold, he's caught a cold, he's caught a cold, he's
caught a cold, he's
caught a cold, he's caught a cold, do that to you, okay,
do it, people, you see, we're going
today, we said we want to
go and eat seafood lovers, but we're
not going because
we always order food when it comes home,
today we're going there, that is, crying about everything there,
so we told you, this is a
Ramadan blog and for  Rezma, so it's
just a break, let's go ahead and
meet, let's meet, let
's go, I would
n't have decided, I would have just wronged her, but I have
problems, why did I give it to her,
we've only arrived at this time, at
11 o'clock, people
are just cleaning, you mother, you are a ghost.
Why have we been like this so much, man?  We
Christians always break our fast, unlike
Muslims.
This is the first time people are cleaning up
this big place.
What is this?
Oh, peanut butter. I don't like peanut butter.
Welcome
to
the fast, you know I have
that strong stomach.  What grass?  Oh, what's the
price,
if we take a lot
now, because it's a lie,
brother, we don't have money, what's this, this
holy month, where do we give money, brother,
because we all don't have money,
no, brother, reduce people, we take
a lot,
that's why I
reduced the others by 4000, 4000, that's why
I said no, I'm
telling you the truth,
brother, don't do this, life is hard, you,
life is hard
here, we got help from the government,
everyone here,
not just you, even me,
life is like
that, you know,
I'm raising three children,
brother, you know, you think you know how many
children,
seven, and their father has abandoned me, it's
not
true, here I am, I'm abandoned, oh, you haven't abandoned me, do
n't lie to me,
why am I abandoned
here, I'm looking for someone to marry, help me raise
those children, the
plan is
just to come and sell clothes, they're all
enough, you've been rejected,
people are cutting me off,
then I'll be the second wife, oh, the power,
because that second wife, I'll be required of everything,
you know, that's what, mashallah, what does he really
get, the first wife, and the second wife,
get the same, it's
hard, what's
hard, first,
this, he rejects me,
tell him I'm a scoundrel,
now you think you're poor,
I'm telling you the truth,
you know the Islamic religious laws are
those when you have one wife, when you have two wives, the
clever Paula
sees serving the truth
when you have two wives, that is, what you give to the
first wife and the second wife, you have to give her that, that, that, if
you deny
her this, you are not here, we do
n't have A.
Helaima
will be a disaster.
Good morning, I don't know if I'll breastfeed you, I
don't know when. I'm
telling you that I'm
fasting, I'm only fasting on the third day, that is, I'm holding my
neck, I was
watching the
children.
How much?
LI is perfect
but the family can pay you a
million so you don't get that
many I
don't know my requests so if you don't get that
many you give me let
us know it's me my requests
20 thousand we bring it guys
today I got
what is coming coming guys
today I got a visit here at
my shop they have come to Masupar two guys a mother
and her child I mean I am very happy
I mean I am very happy I mean it doesn't seem like they are
thieves but today he paid me today he paid
guys the other day they ran away with
my money.
So I'm so happy.  I'm so guys behind the
camera Sean Shawi.  Guys, don't forget to
subscribe, guys, if you get this money for
YouTube, bring me some besties. Ramadhan Karim
for a good rest, guys, forgive me, I have a
cold.  So I was sitting and discussing
with my family, my baby, and my
mother.   I
kept saying that I wanted to have an iftar where
I would be feeding
orphans and some of my
close friends.  At first I wanted to do it at
home, but we realized the space was small
and the number of people was large.  So right now
we've come here to Mwenge, there's a garden,
we've found a decoy to
do the measurements, as you can see the place
is beautiful, very cutesy.  Meshani told me
you will get tired of this cute but I don't care.
It's cute.  So we came to measure and
arrange the whole process.  This one here is
called Pvin, he is the person who will be
decorating to
make sure everything is going well.
Trust
me, I will disappoint, everything will be on
point, I will see for myself.  Everything will
be as discussed.
Okay.
Bye.
The first is rain.  That is, let's be realistic, it
may rain but it is possible that it will not rain that
day, it rained
yesterday, we are catching it like this if
there is moisture, moisture,
now you will still want people to put it somewhere to sit
down,
that is the first mistake and another thing
about the tent, you still want a tent, I still want
trust, sorry, I want trust, I do
n't even understand there, that is, the rain may not
rain, I just pray that it will rain, not rain,
now that is the example, it has rained, it has rained, I
see it as okay
now, if the tent is put in, it will destroy
that, who do you want, you or the tent
will be on standby
or will it just be a tent if it has been sitting,
you can call and put it in, it will be closed, it will go
into the trust, that is, it will be closed,
which is a little bit, but we will look at the
example of the people starting maybe at 12 o'clock,
people will start to
or we will see if tomorrow, the 13th,
look at the arrival of the 11th, right now,
you know, you may be surprised, it has rained, it has rained,
maybe what to do, even if they start at
11 o'clock, already, that is, 11 o'clock, yours at 10 o'clock, 11 o'clock,
we are looking at the hours at 9 o'clock,
10 o'clock, the weather  How is it
today when because
today frid the sixth
that day thursday thursday it will rain
they said
let me
I want because already the place is space
has a big space we would put
people entering they see it really
like this there is
m I like it here because the big space
people will do well
they will leave themselves well
I see and this mira this
mra things of brid shabab not bana you
will be paid there is
no truth you chose this you remember
eh let's do this this this
here this
here
eh
this
now this here will be similar to the
outside entrance we will be there will be no difference the
outside we put we put
and I cried right now the inside should
look like this then again and inside you must
suspect
eh then let me look at this this this this this
is a tent those
arabic tents they tie tarpaulin on m
m
but it has stayed well even if it rains
or what do you think the
rain we have rejected in the name of Jesus there is no rain rain there is no
sindio
eh
hi guys so tomorrow isedday and that is the day
I am going to remove the orphan eh
I got stressed guys so that everything
will be okay m my head is burning  mots
I pray that tomorrow will be a good day that everything
I planned can happen right now
you put him in the salon so that he can prepare
for tomorrow and iftar then
I will go and pick up dad and get him a coat and
I will go buy my clothes so today I
have to do all the preparations let's
go eat because he is applying makeup when he is applying
Rashelewana
ham
those clothes are there
eh I just left him at the salon at this time I came for a coat because a coat,
man I came for a
coat mall
I came for a coat mall to pick up dad and get him a
coat so let's go at this time I'm wearing my
favorite cloth
ch
kivchanuk
let's wear it again I showed him the
big one first
not those sir
eh
now those are the ones that are a
problem at this time these are the problems enough
dread but he has braided he has braided going
back
is one his hair we braided his we braided
his hair the
first ones they give him the
phone he has
gone a
little further you have grown
smaller
with you and
I was wanting me to take this to look
between these two
these are not very big at this time these are the
times I don't know.
No.  Width and height?  No, not 20
strict fasts.
Very
dangerous.
And that's the first time my
head hurts.
Why are you looking at me like that?
They would find me a seat, I feel faint.   I'll stay
here.   I
'm going to check out the venue.  I just came here to
check out the gay Kidawa.   A
drug addict is waiting for her to
come home. She likes princess
treatment. This is the one I'm at the gay.
I'm waiting for her to come.
Then let's go and see if she's finished braiding.
Why are you waiting so much? You want to be followed
here.
Why aren't you ashamed?
I came by school bus. School bus is not a
little bit. It's
time for iftar. Hey, I've finished
preparing everything. I followed Amara to the salon.
So we came. It's time for iftar. This is the hour.
We're still waiting. We've always been there. We're just here.
When I
eat myself, Amara
put a lot of peppers on me. I've grown up.
Why did you put peppers on me? She
likes peppers. And I told them that they
like peppers. She was surprised. I put them
on the Nisa chapati. She was surprised. No, you put them
on the salad.
I told her that she likes peppers. I'm asking you to
return them. You'll be returned.
Bring them on the chapati. You're a sinner. It must have been too late.
That's what this brother said. Why is
iftar here? Hey, it's very beautiful. 10 times.
You look great with your hair.
Oh.
This is a mango.
This is a mango from the back.  Then this is bungo
spice
which is all called Mexican fruit
which includes
mango, mango, chali and bungo
but you put it on top with a popsicle of ice
cream on a stick, the zen and the sauce is
complete with its name called
Mexican Fruit. It
's amazing. We are very full.
Congratulations to Paula
Kajala. So shoutout to them.
Iftar has been amazing. That's the
big thing. We enjoy. We are happy.
Good music.
Very clean. What kind of food is it?
Tell us.
Good food. Delicious. Yummy.
Everything is good.
Who am I talking to? Floyish.
So, how's the food?
Delicious.  The aroma is amazing.
Everything is just fantastic.  Oh my god.
The taste is
perfect, right?  Perfect.  Everything.
Yo, Nasa Kitchen, how are you doing?
I'm fine.  How are you?
I'm good.  So, how's the food?
The food is nice. When can I eat because
I've been hungry for a long time?  But the food
is so nice.  Kisses to the chef.
All of the things you're eating right
now.  What's your favorite?
These are bananas because they are soft.
You know I have a lot of bananas.
Okay,
really, he's closing.
I'm closing
you,
now you have to start closing.
Count.  Eh, I mean, I just knew it
was because there was a date for the
songs to be released, I had to move it forward, so we had to
set a date,
what date are you leaving the dance,
then you've moved it forward, wait and
count, it's not a combination of
Umari, on the road again, or okay, that's why you
don't talk,
that's why you don't talk,
or I'll steal your secret,
oh, I'll tell you the
secret,
it was 15 matches, but Eh, I've
moved forward a little bit,
for the month, for the
month, for
God's sake, it's not a blessing, and it's not Me.
Good bro.
haina
how the food man you enjoying ah sheikhe
kwama naenjoy brother delicious food eh
he has decided to give us sustenance and we have got
sustenance
unco how is it uncle usually
like a kaa how was dubai first of all how has it been
you ran away.
Oh, what do Muslims say?  Alhamdulillah because it was a
sudden thing, but I thank God for returning
safely with things like this.  We are at home
so
I am fine.  I like draft tea, meat,
everything about this food is very good
.  I mean, out of everything, I don't have anything
that stands out above anything else, but
I'm a big fan of noodles.  Now, these
noodles are called second-hand noodles.
Yeah.  I really like these, but everything
here on the buffet
is crap.  It's
for coming,
we haven't seen each other for a long time, you'll find
another one, come and see us,
baby number two, maybe they'll
give birth to a boy,
in fact,
let's bring him, I'll take care of him,
because a boy becomes a beast to
steal,
okay,
where am I? I
told him, Trapenda, he told me,
they've finished, I told him, I
haven't seen them yet, I'm late, congratulations, thank you, you're fine,
old man,
thank you for coming,
I found out this way, maybe there's something more,
I'm just fine,
okay.
Hey, sir, congratulations.  Thank you, cool, congratulations,
congratulations on winning
because you have
truly come out, thank you,
my love,
you are a
gift
and
I want it like he
said,
but let's go in and blow ourselves up
there,
sir, these are just idiots, these are just idiots, congratulations,
thank you, there's a camera here, I'm
telling you, he's just completely trolling me,
say hi to the camera,
man, this is a gossip. Ah.
Ya
Allah
subhanahu
Hello.  Hello.
We were far away from
me,
I loved it, I'm not
like we saw you in the picture, I'm not,
yes, thank you so much, man,
no, don't be ashamed, I loved everything,
man, I trusted him and he, man, he
delivered everything,
I'll thank you for this, let me
take a picture first,
like a dream,
I finished the activity, then I remembered,
my vlog people today haven't
updated and I haven't updated anything,
I was putting on makeup, I was
doing my hair, I was late,
imagine, I got there an hour late, so
I was doing things, that is,
thank you very much to those who came.
I invited many people yesterday and the day before yesterday, but
all of them showed up, I'm glad the
children enjoyed it.
I thank God so much, my case has
gone exactly as I wanted it to.
Thank you Real Moments, our
event sponsors.  Thank you Pavin for the record.
Thank you food lovers for the
food.  Lady Nadja for
perfume.  Sugar for ice cream and that
's another one.  Not for a cocktail.   I
don't think I've forgotten anyone,
man. I'm sorry but thank you guys.
Hey besties it's another beautiful day.
If you remember in my vlog from two
weeks of February, I said that I really love
the shoes.  Now, at my iftar
yesterday, I invited him.  When I invited him,
he came, but an emergency occurred and he had to
leave early.  So we couldn't
greet each other and couldn't even take a
picture.  So I felt really bad.   I
looked for him and told him if he was free,
come and have dinner at home.
So guess what she's coming.  I can't wait
to see her
guys, let's tell a story.  So let's wait
for her.
So this is what I'm wearing.
The dress,
the hair.  Hey guys, I just told you this
hair band is for sale at Miss Meal.  This
hair band really helps me.  Well,
let me show you guys.  Or do you see
my situation?  But when I wear this hair band, I
look like a mermaid.
This hair band really helps me
because I don't need to pin my
wig.   I mean,
I don't know how to explain it, but it's
very helpful.  You guys have to buy these
hair bands.  Available at Miss Mina.
I'm lying here with my underwear on
but if I want to go out with
anything on, I'll wear it. Hey, Teresa has arrived.
She's out. Let me greet her. I'm so excited. Hey, you smell like udi,
my brother.
Oh, it's not udi, what's your name? Anyway,
you smell good.
Mumeta, I'll give you a gift myself.
Listen, listen, look, look.
Oh, he will be happy
.  Oh.
Oh.  And where is he, if he loves music
?  The deposit
is up there.  Wait, I'll call him.
Wait, I'll bring you some food right now,
man.
I hope you have eaten.
I just ate a little ugali and
now you can finish it, calm down
.  So let me bring you here
first, I'm coming right now.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Can you finish all this?   Let me show you,
I was feeling hungry.
What is this?
Milk tea.
You are making tea for me,
mom, so
you can finish it like this, let
me show you, mom, what's the problem?
I want to see if you can finish it or not. I'm showing you that. It gives you there.
Maybe I want
my video to be two minutes long. You say, "Eat it,
finish it in five minutes," so we
can cut it in the middle. I'll eat it all. Then where are you going? Hey, hold on, okay? Okay, okay
Okay.
Hey.
Now, let me show you
this, it's over in two minutes,
or just eat it with your hand.
Oh, I'm not wearing a bracelet.
Why do
I eat so much, I'm not very picky.
You and your twin are the ones who go together
in this sausage and chapati.
Hmm.   I
'm really surprised, I want to see how he
finishes all this food.  Yes,
baby.  Okay.  Sit here.
Juice,
man, isn't it sweet?
So how many times a day do you eat?
I
like 15 times. Eh
mh
how
now I can't put it on camera and
on camera I can't show that
I'm eating because I have to cut cut cut
the video but I always eat
how many kilos you weigh
and you eat 15 times a day and when he went
to the doctor he told me that
like my kilos and my height don't match I have to
eat a lot
so you eat 20 times
m that is that and there is Yes that
.
Oh, you
have to set a date for us, that is, when
you eat, that is, all those times,
because the video has to be short.
That's why, when you're little, my mother
tells me I'm going there.
Amara,
how many times do you eat a day
and you all don't say "
child"
really, man, you're in your first year now, you're not a
child, eh, being a first year is childhood, how old are you, how old are you,
tell me, first, how old are you,
first, I
asked you, first, how old are you,
20,
now I've passed, how many years have I passed, man, four
.  four 24
I'm turning 24 this year
oh
eh
m so
I'm a sister it
can't be
ma I saw I called a child guys people on
insta have attacked me they've attacked me
but still k
but you're younger than me you're the
same as me and my younger brother
who is
my younger brother
and you're giving me away
why
now why have you only eaten a little you've stopped
Eh I cooked
hm delicious food if
you sit in the kitchen you can't eat a lot of food
that is here I'm sitting down so that I can get it
well.
Let us bring you cold water or
hot water.  I can't
believe my eyes, man.
This is it, then leave it alone,
why should I leave it? When
you left home, you ate,
I ate a little,
you
finished with that samosa, then I'll finish.
Okay, everything is
dangerous here.
This is for Amara.  I carried it myself, it wasn't stolen, it
arrived.
Amara is happy and I'm happy.
We're working,
guys. I'm done, so I'm going home.
Paula, you only use that skinx, that's all
you
really want. Skinx things, my gay.
I should try. I have to give it to you. It's really,
really, please and pleas.
Guys. I'm so happy.  I have met the
shoes.
The jeans.  Hey.
The Paula.
She is such a sweet soul.  Guys,
I don't know what to say, you are not just beautiful on the
outside, you have a good soul, you are
beautiful on the inside.  I mean,
thank you very much.  I'm glad to
see you guys.  food for kik
imagine I finished all the food
eh
I ate I don't know two spoons she didn't believe it she finished I did
n't believe it man
I told you I'll show you I do
n't play with food even one day
my grandma made me throw away food
I gave you this greeting
see you next time
hey besties so after making iftar
I posted my dress on snapchat and a
lot of people were like she liked it
man where we ask you to see and all that so
I decided to do a
little challenge I'm putting it there challenge you see for
people who have followed me on snapchat I think
you saw it and a lot of people commented
man he until I got confused
I don't know who to choose the winner but at the end
of the day I found one winner
so yesterday I announced the winner and asked her for
her number then we talked to her so she could come and
pick up her dress.  So he arrived right
now.  Let's go meet her.  This is the
first time I've seen him.  I don't even know him
but I liked his comment.  But I'm
so excited to meet her.  Let's go see her
and give her a dress.  Did you leave college?
Oh, thanks,
I'm glad to see it.
You're embarrassed, you're not a
camera person.
hello vlog people
let's go I don't know hi this is dor so if
you remember there was a pa's challenge
on the dress yeah iftar so i commented
and unfortunately I don't know it's lucky and
yesterday my friend texted me that I want
the challenge so today I got my dress from
Paula.  So, thank you very much Paula for
the dress.  I can't wait to dress this
onid.  Yes, thank you.
The guy told me he's graduating this year.
So I told him I would give him a
gift at his graduation.
Yeah.  I will remind him.
Or I'll give him a suit to wear or anything.
I will check.  Make sure you remind me,
guys, I'm
eating here and doing a little shopping.
So hi,
my hair is like a pea, so it
matches your age.  Relax,
I need someone to help me plan my
43rd birthday party.
So my mother came to visit me here, let's go to
Serena, it was my birthday two days ago,
Sesi, I know many of you
know her.  So my mother was traveling and
I was busy, so we couldn't do
anything for her.  Now we want to take him to the party
and cut him a cake.  So let's
go.  What do you have to say?  Do you have
anything?
Oh okay,
he came.   What's wrong with you?
Get in the car.
I'm not recording Paula on the recorder
because we're recording. What's wrong with you? How do you take it?
Hey, you
take it when something takes
a lot.
But you're really into
Serena.
Because that is,
my mother likes it when I tell her,
then let's go somewhere else, she doesn't want it,
sir, branch serena, everything serena, eh,
my life, I
don't know why, sir, the food is brand new, that
is, if you only eat a little, you are full, you can't
add more, it's not with yeast, I don't understand,
and
you're going to add more,
my stomach is still there,
but this juice, sir, is very good, fashion
mix and watermelon,
welcome,
when are you changing the gene, it's still not yet,
until when, I don't know
Hello.  Hi guys.
So today I met my younger sister,
Amara Serena, and we ate while you fasted.
Yes, you are
fasting for those sins.   I'm
closing.
I'm happy to see you.  I'm so proud of
you.  Thank you.
I'm so proud of you.  Your vlog is great,
keep it up and don't get discouraged.
Thank you,
I saw that you have become an entrepreneur.
Thank you.
I'm waiting for you and you are very busy.
Mashallah.
Thank you.
Bye-
bye.   I
have to take sweet pineapples little by little so I don't spill it all
on the counter and get bitten.
You chew and then one mother tell me
I cut you off,
man, if
he chews badly, all the videos, delete, delete,
even you, you, tell me how you chew, how do you
hate someone who eats like a
thief, that is, you know when you know everything
here, I am a
little shocked, that's why you chew like that,
you, lady, you are
wrong, now
I know that vog, you are
ruining your reality show,
its life,
if you are bugging, you are bugging,
I am putting people on vlogs, don't you see, man, I am
beating you
again, I am constantly fighting, because it seems that
you know your eating, you know the
eating of force, maybe
something bad, that is,
I chew badly, it comes alone,
but when I eat, I will not chew badly,
what do you have to attack me?  I'm tired of
chewing on that myself.
You know who's there, very beautiful,
check it out,
my mother is jealous of me, so the dress is
beautiful, she says,
bye